

kjuneja0706@gmail.com | 562-308-0036 | Round Rock, Texas 78665

Summary

A Quality Engineer with more than two years of professional experience in Google's Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Natural Language Understanding (NLU) system. Experience in analyzing data from Google search engine and optimizing the search results by improving query understanding using machine learning models. Excellent time management and problem solving skills. Highly organized, multi-tasker and a quick learner who is enthusiastic to take up new challenges.

Skills

- Programming Language: C/C++, SQL, CSS, HTML, JavaScript, JAVA, Python, VB Script
- Tools: Eclipse, Dream Viewer, GitHub, Wire Shark, Anaconda, QT, Selenium Web Driver, TestNG, MSSQL, Maven, Jenkins, Visual Studio Code.
- Framework: Agile, SCRUM, Waterfall, SDLC, STLC, BDD, DDF

Experience

UT Austin | Austin, TX

Data Analytics and Visualization Boot

Camp Student

06/2021 - Current

- Prepared forecasts and identified trends through data analysis and tracking.
- Compiled current business intelligence data into reports and presentations.
- Identified new products and sources based upon consumer behavior and marketing results.
- Assessed data and issues and directed concerns to business unit leadership.
- Analyzed product, market and share trends to evaluate competitive market strategies.
- Collected, tracked and organized data to evaluate current business and market trends.
- Organized subsystems to execute proper collection of data

QualiTest Group | Austin, Texas SLS Quality Engineer 09/2019 - Current

- Provide natural native-language expertise for a wide range of topic areas and help to define software needs.
- Serve as expert "raters" for specific products, for engineers working on improving the software.
- Analyze data and further related analysis.
- Work with Search Engineers for advanced algorithm development.
- Diagnose and report results.
- UI and Product improvement.
- Help adjust the user interfaces to the local languages.
- Write configuration documents for explanations

California State University Los Angeles | Los Angeles, CA

• Work one-to-one and in small groups with students on specific course

Instructional Student Assistant

10/2016 - 05/2019

- related assignments.
- Assit students to better prepare, improve their knowledge and understanding, and develop the skills for college success.
- Served as a study skills development workshop presenter and new tutor trainer.

Education and Training

California State University - Los Angeles | Los Angeles, CA **Bachelor of Science** in Computer Science

Activities and Honors

- Member of the National Society of Leadership and Success.
- Member of Golden Key International Honour Society.

Academic Projects

Sea-Food Service Supreme: [Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Java Script, Selenium WebDriver, TestNG, Extend Report, Git, Jenkins]

To provide an online website for users to register for an account, place orders, track orders, and review order history and provide a live-feed video of our livestock for our users to pick and choose from. Project was also to test the web application manually and then to automate the test cases.

Resume Management: [Technologies used: Microsoft Access]

This project is designed in Microsoft Access to model a database system for creating tables, forms, reports to keep a record of resumes.

Inventory System for Pharmacy: [Technologies used: Microsoft Excel]

Inventory System Project was designed in Microsoft Excel to maintain the inventory for all the medicines. To fetch the medicines from the inventory easily.

Accomplishments

- Dean's List (Fall 2014)
- Tech Savvy Award
- International Baccalaureate Learner Profile Award for being Principled and for being Inquirer.

Certifications

- Complete Python Bootcamp
- Leadership: Practical Leadership Skills
- R Programming A-Z: R For Data Science
- The Business Intelligence Analyst